Everybody always says they want to go
running with me until they see the
places that we're going to go running.
Usually I'm here in flip-flops
in mountains like this.
That's where we going.
Way up there, pig dog.
No food, no water,
not even a pair of closed-toed shoes.
Just a hope and a prayer
trying to find out how much is inside my
soul
on a regular basis.
And
I just don't know how many
humans
are left
that enjoy like this.
But one day
I'm going to find another friend
after Austin left me two summers ago.
And man,
I'll just tell you it might look stupid,
but if you ever get addicted to
discipline and self-improvement, you'll
never go back.